女主人，打我的屁股！ 用力打
MAN 1 ON COMPUTER.; Mistress, spank my bottom. spank it really hard!
拜托，打我屁股！
Please, spank my bottom!
- 看了真不舒服 - 用力打
-That is unpleasant. -spank it really hard.
舔我的乳头
wOMAN ON COMPUTER.; Lick my nipples.
不，谢了，这位孕妇
No, thank you, pregnant lady.
脱掉，士兵！ 他们叫我大炮教官不是叫假的
MAN 2 ON COMPUTER.; strip, soldier! You're gonna find out why they call me the drill sergeant.
那...感觉真棒，宝贝
That's... That's nice, baby.
不，卷毛！ 不要啊！
No, Frizzy! No!
不，卷毛！ 不要！
No, no, no, Frizzy! No!
卷毛
Frizzy. (PHONE BEEPs)
不，等等！ 柯弟！ 不
No, no, no, wait! Cody! No.
不，卷毛！ 不要！
ROB ON PHONE.; No, no, no, Frizzy! No!
别担心，老兄 每个人都有性爱录影带
Don't worry about it, man. Everyone's got a sex tape.
拜托
Please.
对，但他们的对象都是人
Yeah, except they're having sex with people.
- 卷毛 - 对
-(GRO ANING) Frizzy. -Right.
不同种的家族成员 技术上来说不算乱伦
lt's not technically incest if your family member's a different species.
有没有成功上了黛娜？
so, are you getting close with Dana yet?
谣言是真的，她要守贞
The rumors are true. she's taken the pledge.
不做爱？ 你本来是可以上她的
No sex? she was your sure thing.
- 信望爱那套，老兄 - 她要等到结婚才做
-Faith-camp propaganda, man. -NATHAN: she's waiting until marriage.
我以为她睡过六个人了
l thought she had sex with six guys.
怎样啦？
What?
去上课了
Get to class.
走廊不准讲手机，艾莉森
No cell phones in the hall, Alyson.
放学后再到办公室找我领
You can pick this up from my office today after school.
不，卷毛！ 不！ 卷毛！
No, no, no, Frizzy! No! Frizzy!
我看过更糟的
Well, l've seen worse.
不，卷毛！ 不要！
No, no, no, Frizzy! No!
强森小姐，一起吃午餐？
Miss Johnson. Lunch today?
我要查一下行事历 痞...彼特
l'll have to check my calendar, perv... Pete.
不，卷毛！ 不！ 卷毛！
No, no, no, Frizzy! No! Frizzy!
看啊，看看这个
Look. Look. Look at that.
不，卷毛！ 不！ 卷毛！
No, no, no, Frizzy! No! Frizzy!
- 嘿，别理她们 - 天啊，你也看到了？
-Hey, Just ignore them. -Oh, God. You saw it, too?
- 其实不是那样... - 嘿，别担心
-Just so you know, it's not at all... -Hey, don't worry about it.
卷毛是只漂亮的狗
Frizzy's a good-looking dog.
所以你要去吗？ 我们一起？
so, do you wanna do it? Are we on?
罗伯？ 一起去上第七节课？
Rob? Rob? Are we on for seventh period?
对，我...我...
Yeah. l... l'll...
- 课堂上见 - 好的
-l'll meet you over there. -Okay.
- 狗爬式！ - 嘿，史提弗
-Doggy style! -Hey, stifler.
那是你女朋友？
ls that your girlfriend?
不，我们只是...只是朋友
No, we're Just... We're Just... We're friends.
只是朋友？ 真甜蜜
Just friends? How sweet.
嗯，她看起来真成熟 如果你不吃，我可要吃了
Well, she seems awful ripe. lf you don't pick the fruit, l will.
嘿，美女
sTlFLER: Hey, beautiful.
哇！
sTlFLER: Wow!
早安，东瀑高中光芒队
CHARLEs ON PA.; Good morning, East Great Falls Blazers.
别忘了本周 对抗中央高中的球赛
Don't forget about the big game against Central this week
还有周五晚上7点到午夜 有夏威夷舞会
and the Aloha Dance this Friday from 7.;00 to midnight.
入场建议穿夏威夷衫、戴花环
Hawaiian shirts and leis are recommended for entrance.
- 查尔斯，住手 - 抱歉
-PRINCIPAL ON PA.; Charles, knock that off. -sorry.
考试专心点，拜托
Let's focus on the quiz, please.
讨厌鬼
Douche bag.
我对守贞的誓言很认真
l'm serious about this pledge, you know.
我知道
l know.
- 所以今晚只能跳舞 - 好，跳舞就好
-so Just dancing tonight. -Yeah. Just dancing.
一起床上呼啦吧
The horizontal hula.
纳森
Nathan.
可怜的纳森
Poor Nathan.
现在他的鸡鸡 大概硬得可以切玻璃了
His willy must be hard enough to cut glass by now.
纳森爱我，他尊重我
Nathan loves me, and Nathan respects me.
首先，男孩再尊重女孩 也不会放弃性爱
Okay. A, a guy never respects a girl enough to give up sex.
其次，你自己呢？
And, B, well, what about you?
你现在也情欲高涨了吧，黛娜
You must be feeling pretty randy by now, Dana.
好吧，嗯，也许有一点点
Okay, well, yeah, maybe, like, the tiniest bit,
但我真的觉得 我和上帝更接近了
but l really feel like l'm connecting with the higher power here.
我知道，那样很好
Yes, l know, and that is totally fab,
但是我做不到 我太喜欢吹萧了
but l know l couldn't do it. l'm way too into giving blow Jobs.
你问理查
Ask Richard.
嘿，别听伊茉珍的
Hey, don't listen to lmogen, okay?
性爱是重大决定 如果你觉得还没准备好
sex is a really big deal, and if you feel like you're not ready,
我认为你就该再等等
then l think you should wait.
但是...
DANA: But...
恕我直言，海蒂，但你不知道 自己在说什么
No offense, Heidi, but you have no idea what you're talking about.
再传简讯给我
Text me later.
- 嘿，罗伯 - 啥事？
-Hey, Rob. -ROB: Yeah?
- 可以问你一件事吗？ - 当然，什么事？
-Can l ask you something? -sure. What's up?
嗯，挺私人的事
Well, it's kind of personal.
好
Okay.
我一直在想 你知道我是处女吧？
l've been thinking. You know l'm a virgin, right?
只是...我不知道
lt's Just... l don't know.
大家好像都做过无数次了
Everyone's already done it like a million times already,
我知道我没有男朋友 但是...
and l know l don't have a boyfriend or whatever, but...
有时我觉得该克服此事
But sometimes l feel like l should Just get it over with.
我是说快点结束整件事，处女的事
You know? l mean, Just get past this whole thing, this virgin.
那到底有什么意义？
What does that even mean, anyway?
我的阴道没有小弟弟进去过 那又怎样？
so l've never had a penis in my vagina, but so what?
为何他们凡事就针对我？ 像是她太天真了
Why do l have to label everything? Like, ''she's too innocent.
“她无法应付的” 我没那么天真
''she can't handle it.'' l'm not that innocent.
我看过 《美国舞娘》 和 《蓝色珊瑚礁》
l've seen showgirls and Blue Lagoon.
总之，我决定要去做了 你觉得如何？
Anyways, l think l've decided to Just do it. But what do you think?
对，我认为你绝对该赶快 彻底解决这件事
Yeah. l think you should definitely go ahead and get it over with.
谢谢
(LAUGHs) Thanks.
该回去工作了
Let's get back to work.
史提弗将为您 现场实况转播夏威夷舞会
stifcam coming at you live from the Aloha Dance
这里是东瀑高中...
here at the East Great Falls...
这个辣妹刚捏我屁股
This chick Just grabbed my ass.
她八成想和我的小弟弟玩
she wants to play the stifmeister's flute skin.
我们去找些辣妹吧，吉布
Let go find some of that sweet-looking pinoche, Gibbsy.
嘿，看啊，海蒂在那里
Hey, check it out. There's Heidi.
好的，她看来秀色可餐
LUBE: All right, all right. she looks highly doable.
好，所以你的计划是什么？
All right, so what's the game plan here?
我不知道，邀她跳舞吧
l don't know. Ask her to dance, l guess.
你需要计划，好吗？ 这是要建立你的企图心
You need a plan, all right? lt's all about establishing your intentions.
现在她只当你是朋友
see, right now, she thinks of you as Just a friend.
你要打破这种形式
You need to break that paradigm.
记住，好朋友 不会让你和她只做普通朋友
Remember, friends don't let friends Just be friends.
- 好 - 我说真的，你不能退缩
-Right. -l'm serious. You cannot puss out here.
好啦，别激动 我过去找她聊聊
All right, take it easy. l'm gonna go talk to her.
等等，你是否忘了这个？
Wait. Aren't you forgetting something?
还有，别忘了这个
Here, don't forget these.
那是你没伴才会用到的
You only need those when you're alone.
好，好吧
Right. Right. Okay.
- 够了！ - 怎么了？
-(EXCLAlMs) Okay! -What? What's wrong?
我不能
l can't.
- 但我才上二垒耶 - 我知道，但如果上了二垒
-But it's only second base. -l know. But if we go there,
就会继续前进
then we're gonna wanna go further.
可是亚当和夏娃就做了
But Adam and Eve did it.
对不起，嘿
(GAsPs) l'm sorry. Hey, hey.
我爱你，你知道吧？
l love you. Do you know that?
过来
Come here.
上帝可以接受口交吗？
ls God okay with a blow Job?
我以为你了解我的感受
l thought you understood how l felt about this.
我告诉过你 我要把完整的自己留到新婚之夜
l told you, it's important for me to save myself until marriage.
你上过七个男人了
You've had sex with seven guys.
只有六个，不是七个！
And it was six, not seven!
其中一个是黑人 因此他可以抵上两个人
Well, one was a black guy, so he counts as two.
黛娜
Dana.
- 黛娜 - 去死啦
-Dana, come on. -Fuck off.
黛娜，拜托你，黛娜！
Dana. Come on, Dana. Dana!
嘿，女孩们 这会上传到我的脸书哦
Hey, girls. This is gonna be for sit-on-my-face-book.
我要你们互吻一下，好吗？
l need you to kiss one time, okay?
我不知道好不好
l don't know.
来嘛，会有上百万人点阅的
Come on. lt's gonna be seen by millions of people.
好吧
(LAUGHs) Okay.
好，我们再来一次
Okay, we're gonna go again,
但是这一次 喇舌给我们看看
but this time, sneak in some tongue for daddy.
好
Okay.
这就是我在说的，宝贝！
(HlGH-PlTCHED VOlCE) That's what l'm talking about, baby!
史提弗再次击出安打！
stifmeister strikes again!
老兄
Dude.
你会爱死这个的，看啊
You're gonna love this. Check this out.
嗯，所以呢？
Yeah. so?
学着点
Watch and learn.
你很辣
''You're hot.
“给我你的号码 让我们来爽一下”
''Give me your number and let's get together.''
我把这个丢给辣妹
l throw this at a hot girl,
她绝对忘不了 我朝她丢了张百元大钞
and she's so impressed that l'm literally throwing around a BenJamin
所以她会和我上床
that she wants to hook up with me.
嗯，祝你好运
Yeah. Good luck with that.
- 我要去找黛娜 - 好吧，老兄
-l'm gonna go find Dana. -All right, man.
哦，不妙
Oh, no.
哦，天啊
Oh, God.
借过、借过 小心点，我要过去
Excuse me. Excuse me. Watch out. Coming through.
我一直在想 我们之前讨论的事
so, l was thinking about what we were talking about, you know, before.
- 对，我记得 - 对，我在想，何必等呢？
-Yeah. Yeah, l remember. -Right. so l was thinking, why wait?
对吧？ 你也想摆脱那个称号
Right? l mean, you might as well, you know, get it over with.
什么？ 在这里？ 在舞池中？
What? Like, here? At the dance?
学校总有图书馆啊
Well, there's always the library.
- 对，图书馆 - 开玩笑的
-Yeah, the library. -l'm kidding.
- 嗯，我知道 - 但说真的，舞会之后
-Yeah. l know. -But seriously, after the dance,
我不知道你是否...
l don't know if you...
- 你在干嘛？ - 找我的钱
-What are you doing? -Looking for my money.
- 百元大钞？ - 对
-C-note thing? -Yeah.
- 钱不见了？ - 闭嘴
-Lose your money? -shut up.
我们回来了，怎么回事？ 海蒂人呢？
And we're back. What's up, dude? Where's Heidi?
我不知道
l don't know.
- 她刚还在这里的 - 也许去厕所了
-she was here a second ago. -Maybe she went to the bathroom.
- 对，也许 - 黛娜在生我的气
-Yeah, maybe. -Dana's pissed at me.
你必须忍耐这整个守贞的事
Dude, you gotta play along with this whole pledge thing.
你说得倒容易
Well, that's easy for you to say.
你也还没破处男之身啊
You haven't exactly broken the seal yet, either.
老兄，我上三垒都已经习以为常了
Dude, l've been getting to third base on a regular basis.
不能回头再去打手枪
l can't go back to Jacking off now.
老兄，改用你的左手 感觉会完全不一样
Dude, Just use your left hand. lt feels completely different.
- 我要去找海蒂 - 我要去找黛娜
-l'm gonna go find Heidi. -l'm gonna go find Dana.
不！ 老兄，你让我想吐
BOY: (LAUGHs) No! Dude, you're gonna make me hurl.
海蒂？
Heidi?
不、不、不！
LUBE: No, no, no, no!
等等
Wait.
老兄，嘿
Dude, yo.
你在干什么？
What are you doing?
罗伯？ 你说...
Rob? You said...
罗伯！
Rob!
老兄，你真是电灯泡啊
Dude, nice cock block.
我着火了
l'm on fire.
- 我着火了 - 天啊
-l'm on fire. -Oh, my God.
失火了，我身上着火了
There's a fire. There's a fire, and it's on me.
我的天
Oh, my God.
罗伯！ 快弄熄，脱掉裤子！ 脱掉...脱掉你的裤子！
HElDl: Rob! Rob! Put it out. Take off your pants! Take off... Take your pants off!
天啊！
Oh, God!
快点！
(sHRlEKs) Come on!
我的天啊！ 天啊！
Oh, my God. Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
快点，罗伯，快啦
Hurry, Rob, come on.
弄熄它！ 弄熄它！
Get it out! Get it out!
天啊
Oh, God.
这里到底怎么了？
What the hell is going on in here?
连续两个月周六留校 似乎太长了
Two months seems like an awfully long time for saturday detention.
我们要打扫图书馆
We're supposed to clean up the library.
你们知道吸尘器放哪了？
Do you guys know where the vacuum is?
不知
Nope.
你到底去图书馆做什么？
What were you doing in the library anyway?
我什么也没做 海蒂已经在那里了
l wasn't doing anything. Heidi was already in there.
- 我只是去找她 - 听说她在帮人吹萧
-l was Just looking for her. -l heard she was blowing some dude.
柯弟！ 我不知道你被留校劳动
Cody! Well, l don't know how you're gonna go on the school ski trip
怎么参加学校的滑雪之旅
if you're still on detention.
妈，我不懂为何处罚我 我又没做什么
Mom, l don't see what that has to do with it. l didn't do anything.
我听说你是负责助性的
l heard you were the fluffer.
- 柯弟 - 看，他的嘴唇都龟裂了
-Cody. -Look. His lips are chapped.
嗯，再说吧
Well, we'll see.
我必须去准备了
All right. l have to go get ready.
也许放在车库
Maybe it's in the garage.
罗伯？ 我想和你聊聊
Rob? l wanna have a little chat with you.
一定要吗？
Do we have to?
儿子，我知道你越来越大了
Honey, l know that you're growing older,
我不知道你爸有没有教你
and l don't know what your father has told you about things,
但我认为我们该无所不谈，对吧？
but l think it's important to discuss everything, you know?
例如性爱
Like about sex.
- 你有性关系了？ - 妈，我不想谈这个
-Are you having sex? -Mom, l don't wanna talk about this.
嗯，只是我在车库找到这只袜子...
No, well, it's Just that l found this sock in the laundry, and, well...
天啊，妈，快拿开
Oh, God, Mom. Put that away.
还有，某人寄了段影片给我
And, also, somebody sent me a link to this video.
不，卷毛！ 不要！
ROB.; No, no, no, Frizzy! No.
- 妈，关掉啦！ - 我不会关！
-Mom, Just turn it off! -l don't know how!
你弟弟把它设定成开机画面
Your brother made it my start-up screen.
- 好，我来改设定 - 你会？ 太好了
-Okay, l can... l can fix that. -You can? Great.
- 嗯 - 谢谢
-Yeah. -Thanks.
- 不，卷毛！ 不要！ - 谢谢你
-No, no, no, Frizzy! No! -Thank you for that.
- 好 - 我们谈完了吧？ 行了
-Okay. -And we're done. Right? Yeah.
亲爱的，拜托 你不必觉得丢脸
Well, honey, please. There's no reason to be ashamed.
自慰是很正常的事
Masturbation is perfectly natural.
像你这种年纪的男孩 或许喜欢实验
l mean, boys your age are maybe into experimentation
尝试点新的，和动物试试
and trying new things with animals.
可是卷毛从小... 它是我们家的一份子...
l mean, Frizzy, she's been in our family for... since she was a puppy...
嘿，我迟到了
(sTAMMERs) Hey, l'm late.
- 你迟到了 - 抱歉
-You're tardy. -sorry.
你可以开始清理 那些受损的书
You can start by cleaning off all the damaged books
把烧坏的分开来 我会来检查的
and separating the ruined ones. l'll be checking on you.
海蒂，昨晚的事...
Heidi. Look, about last night...
我不想谈这个
l don't wanna talk about it.
- 嗯，我只想告诉你... - 罗伯
-Well, l Just wanted to tell you... -Rob.
水满了，我去倒掉
l'm gonna go empty this bucket.
宝典
重要须知！
看我找到什么？
Do you have any idea what l found here?
- 这是宝典耶 - 我以为只是传说
-This is the bible. -l thought that was an urban legend.
不，这是真的，数十年前就有了
No. This is real. This goes back decades.
好，所以呢？
Okay. so what?
想要真的和女生上床 我们就需要这个
This is exactly what we need to finally get laid.
这如何让我们和女生上床？ 都烧坏了
How is this thing gonna help us get laid? lt's ruined.
几乎无法阅读了
You can't even read most of it.
这本书每年都帮助 一名幸运的东瀑学生
This book has helped one lucky guy each year at Great Falls.
今年的幸运学生就是我们
And this year, that lucky guy is us.
就算烧坏了 里面还是有一堆有用资料，你们看
Even with the damage, it still has a ton of useful stuff. Check this out.
“1977年2月1日，G点”
''February 1st, 1977. The G-spot.''
- 我喜欢 - 还有什么？
-l can dig it. -LUBE: What else you got?
“1991年，如何修剪阴毛 让小鸡鸡看起来大一点”
''1991 . How to shave your pubes to make your dick look bigger.''
我爸教过我这招
Dad showed me that one.
“2003年 我有过最棒的性爱经验”
''2003. l Just had the most amazing sexual experience.''
有些烧坏了看不到 “她用了口腔芳香剂”
something l can't read. ''she used a breath mint.''
口腔芳香剂？ 干嘛用的？
A breath mint? For what?
笨蛋，你让她把那个 伸进你的小菊花，超刺激的
You moron. You stick it up your tailpipe and the minty-ness makes your asshole twitch.
大家都知道啊
Everyone knows that.
天啊，我不知道，这个似乎很怪
Dude, l don't know. This sounds pretty weak.
况且这些绝大多数 网路就找得到了
Plus, l mean, we can find most of this stuff on the internet anyway.
不，这不一样 里面有个人的经验
No, this is different. This has personal experiences.
况且是针对东瀑女孩 量身撰写的
Plus, it's custom-tailored to Great Falls girls.
曾几何时 连阴道都有邮递区号了？
since when does punani have a zip code?
我们有什么损失？ 纳森 你一直想搞定黛娜，多久了？
What have we got to lose? Nathan, you've been working on Dana for, what?
六个月了吧？ 结果只发现 她爱上帝胜过做爱
Like six months? Only to find out that she loves the Lord more than sex?
还有你，路伯 你那些做爱计划有效吗？
And, Lube, how have all your schemes to get laid been working out so far?
损失了一百元
Minus $100.
没错，至于我 我一直在幻想有一天
Exactly, and me, well, l've been wasting all my time on some fantasy that someday
海蒂将会爱上我 面对现实吧，各位，我们需要帮助
Heidi's gonna fall madly in love with me. Face it, guys, we need help.
就是这个，答案就在我们面前
And this is it, staring us right in the face.
- 我加入 - 好耶
-l'm in. -All right.
算我一份
l'm in.
- 耶 - 好耶
-Yeah. -Yes.
- 耶！ - 耶！
-Yeah! -Yeah!
轻点，这书很旧了
Hey, easy. Guys, it's old.
1990年5月1日
''May 1st, 1990.
“钻进女生裤子 最简单的方法还是吹捧”
''The simplest way into a girl's pants is still basic flattery.''
就这样？ 只要捧她？
That's it? Just flatter her?
- 就是这样 - 嗯，想一想
-That's it. -Well, think about it.
你真正捧过她几次？
How many times do you actually do it?
走过去对女孩说 “哇，你的眼睛真美”
Walk up to a girl and say, ''Wow, you have beautiful eyes.''
从来没有，它教导我们 把女人的唯一方法是当笨蛋
Like, never. lt's telling us the only proven way to get women is to be an asshole,
因为会说这些话的男人 才把得到妹
'cause the guys that actually spew that kind of crap get laid.
注意看，十二点钟方向
Check it out. Twelve o'clock.
- 好，来测试一下这本宝典 - 好
-All right. Let's put this bible to a test. -Yes.
- 你去搭讪 - 我不要拿爱西莉做测试
-You go talk to her. -l'm not trying it out on Ashley.
你为什么不去？ 你才是喜欢她的那个人
Why don't you go talk to her, 'cause you're the one who likes her?
- 我在吃东西 - 好，我去
-l'm eating. -Okay. l'll do it.
嘿，爱西莉
Hey, Ashley.
嘿，罗伯，买礼物给女朋友？
Hey, Rob. shopping for your girlfriend?
不...这是...给我妈的
No... This is... lt's for my mom.
她又开始约会了
she's dating again.
我...事实上我只想说
Well, you know, l... Actually, l wanted to say,
你的牙齿真的好漂亮
you know, you have the most gorgeous teeth.
嘿，跟我来
Hey. Come with me.
吃醋吗？ 他对你的梦中情人 采取行动了
Jealous? He's making a move on your lady friend.
我不像你，我不介意分享女人
Unlike you, l don't mind sharing my women.
你们两个白痴在干嘛？
(LAUGHs) And what are you wankers up to today?
- 哈罗 - 嗨，亲爱的
-(lN BRlTlsH ACCENT) Cheerio. -(lN BRlTlsH ACCENT) Hello, love.
问候你老妈
Word to your mumsie.
只是等几个女孩加入我们
Just waiting for some ladies to Join us, in fact.
就算握有一叠 强纳斯兄弟演唱会的后台通行证
You nancy boys couldn't get laid at a Jonas Brothers concert
你们两个孬种也把不到女孩，再见喽
with a fistful of backstage passes. Cheerio.
她在侮辱人吗？
(lN NORMAL ACCENT) Was that a slam?
当然啊，笨鸟蛋
(lN NORMAL ACCENT) You bet your bollocks.
- 拿着 - 好
-Hold this. -Yeah.
看起来如何？
How does this look?
很好，我买了
Great, l'll take it.
站起来
stand up.
等等，这...等等
Wait, what... What's... Wait, hold... Hold on.
我再打给你？
should l call you?
走出专柜，到美食街和我会合
Just walk out of the store and meet me at the food court.
表现得自然些
Act natural.
我能帮忙吗？
Can l help you?
不，我...随便逛逛
No. No. l'm... l'm Just browsing.
好吧
Okay, then.
- 祝你今天顺心 - 你也一样
-Have a nice day. -You, too.
抱歉！ 我没偷东西 这是...是开玩笑的
l'm sorry! l wasn't stealing. lt was a... lt was a prank.
真抱歉，我好像忘了拆吊牌
l am so sorry. l think we left the tags on your garments.
请回到柜台 我会弄好的，真不好意思
Please come back to the register. We'll figure this out. l'm so embarrassed.
我的天
Oh, my God.
抱歉，我...我太兴奋了
sorry, l... l got excited.
总共149.90元
That'll be 1 49.90.
- 多少？ - 149.90元
-How much? -1 49.90.
那么小件耶
But they're so small.
- 玛德莲？ - 是我妈的，我...她批准的
-Madeleine? -lt's my mom. l'm... l have a note.
- 谢谢 - 祝你顺心
-Thank you. -Have a nice day.
欢迎再度光临
Come again.
你怎么那么久？ 拿到没？
What took you so long? Did you get it?
当然，我还偷了袋子 这样你就能拎着回家
sure did. l even stole you a bag so you don't have to touch it till you get home.
真好，谢谢
Great. Thanks.
嘿，你好吗？ 爱西莉
Hey. What's up, Ashley?
你们这些娘炮来干嘛？
What are you pillow biters doing here?
史提弗
stifler.
别吃那个，你会变胖
Don't eat that. You're gonna get fat.
我好想来一发 到电器行来帮我吹？
l'm super horny. Wanna suck me off in the sharper lmage?
好啊
Okay.
黛娜，对不起，我很抱歉
(WHlsPERlNG) Dana. Excuse me. l'm so sorry.
我无意打断这... 这个晨间弥撒
Didn't mean to disrupt the... This morning's mass.
你来干什么？
(WHlsPERlNG) What are you doing here?
我想向你道歉
l wanted to say l'm sorry.
现在不适合讨论这个吧？
Did you really think that this is the best time to discuss this?
你不肯回我简讯
Well, you weren't answering any of my texts.
- 我马上回来，好吗？ - 好
-l'll be right back, okay? -(WHlsPERlNG) Okay.
信心是什么？
PRIEsT ON PA.; what is faith?
当你打开厨房的电灯开关
when you flip the light switch in your kitchen,
你知道电灯会亮
you know that the light will turn on.
有人说这就是信心 但我告诉你，这不是真正的信心
some might call that faith, but I tell you, that is not the real faith.
好，什么事那么重要 非要过来打断我听道？
Okay, so what is so important that you needed to come and interrupt church?
我不懂你现在为何那么气我
l don't really get why you're so mad at me right now.
因为你不尊重我 你觉得这一切是个大笑话
Because you don't respect me. This is all Just a big Joke to you.
你说得对，因为这只是 你的另一个阶段
You know what? You're right, because this is Just another phase for you.
就像你年鉴上的声明
Just like your little stint on yearbook.
你能坚守多久 两个星期就腻了？
You stuck with that for, what, two weeks before you got bored with it?
你为何就不能相信 我要等到
Why is it so hard for you to believe that l wanna
结婚之后才有性生活？
(ON PA) wait until marriage?
因为你同一个晚上 睡过道格惠勒和史考特汤姆森
NATHAN ON PA.; Because you slept with Doug wheeler and scott Thompson on the same night.
那不算，我喝醉了
DANA.; That doesn't count. I was drunk.
那是黛娜？
(WHlsPERlNG) ls that Dana?
等你对守贞的事厌烦了
As soon as you get bored with this whole pledge thing,
你又会立刻大干特干
you're just gonna jump right back in the saddle again.
等你上大学以后，别告诉我
And when you get to college, don't even tell me
你不会想试试 标准的女同性爱
that you won't be experimenting with the standard lesbian hookups,
3P性爱、走后门等等
having three-ways, trying anal.
- 耶 - 耶
-Yeah. -Yeah.
- 我就说嘛... - 好，别激动
That's what l'm talking... (LAUGHs NERVOUsLY) Fine. Just relax.
- 想点办法！ - 信心是...
-Do something! -PRIEsT.; Faith is...
- 她是你女儿 - 快去！
-she's your daughter. -Go!
信心如磐石...
PRIEsT.; Faith is the rock-solid...
你认为我做不到？ 我爸妈就守到新婚之夜
DANA.; You don't think I'm committed to this? My parents waited until marriage.
我爸和你妈一起上高中
NATHAN.; (LAUGHs) My dad went to high school with your mom.
他说她帮整个足球队吹过
He said she blew the whole football team
吹到必须去洗胃
and had to have her stomach pumped.
少恶心了，行吗？
DANA.; Don't be gross, okay?
况且你爸是兄弟会的
Plus, your dad was a Beta.
那些家伙超爱办事的
Those guys are notorious poon slayers.
去你的！ 全是胡扯！
Fuck it! This is bullshit!
你知道你想要的
You know you want this.
我们错过圣餐了？
Did we miss communion?
光芒队加油！
(sTUDENTs CHEERlNG)
东瀑光芒队这场比赛 打得很辛苦...
COMMENTATOR 1 ON PA.; Been a rough go for the East Great Falls Blazers in this game...
- 加油，光芒！ - 加油！
CHEERLEADERs: Go, Blazers!
...这真让人吃惊 因为这是本季最后一场主场赛
...which is surprising, since this is the last home game of the season.
大家以为他们会火力全开
You'd think they'd really pump up the power there.
看着他！ 守住他！ 守住他！
Look at him! Watch that guy! Watch that guy!
虽然两队接近平手 但我们原本希望防御更好些...
Even though it's close to a tie, we were hoping for better defense from the...
我的天，等等 你爸怎么说？
Oh, my gosh, wait. so, what did your dad say?
他说如果看到 纳森接近我30公尺范围
He said if he ever sees Nathan within 100 feet of me,
他要拿松土耙阉了他
he's gonna castrate him with a rusty Garden Weasel.
真糟，所以呢？ 你们之间玩完了？
Oh, no. so what? ls it over between you guys or what?
我不知道
l don't know.
如果你想尝试3P 欢迎加入我和理查
Well, if you ever want to try a menage, you're welcome to Join Richard and me.
- 不了 - 不了
-No. -No.
请别在达力教练面前 提到 “年轻男孩”
COMMENTATOR 1.; Please don't say ''young boy'' around Coach Daly.
对，他...
COMMENTATOR 2 ON PA.; Yeah, out here he's...
- 你呢？ 小姐 - 怎样？
-What about you, missy? -What?
你的性生活如何？
How's your sex life?
各位，我要跨出一步了 我说真的
You guys, l'm gonna go through with it. l am. l am.
你真无趣 我还以为图书馆脱衣事件后
You're so boring. l would've thought you'd be fielding offers
你就豁出去了
after your striptease in the library.
对，我... 我还在等适当时机
Yeah, l'm... l'm still Just waiting for the right time.
蓝与白，加油，赢得胜利 加油，赢得胜利
CHEERLEADERs: Blue and white, let's go, fight, win. Let's go, fight, win.
蓝与白，加油，光芒队！
Blue and white, let's go, fight, win. Blazers!
赢得胜利 蓝与白，加油，赢得胜利
Fight, win. Blue and white, let's go, fight, win.
我想你拍够啦啦队的照片了
l think that is quite enough pictures of the cheerleaders.
拍些球赛的照片吧？
How about we get some of the game?
继续拍吧
As you were.
讨厌鬼
Douche bag.
蓝与白...
CHEERLEADERs: Blue and white...
席尔森运球过中场 把球传给史考特史提弗
COMMENTATOR 1.; shearson's bringing the ball up court. He passes it off to scott stifler.
中央队撂倒席尔森
Central takes a charge from shearson.
暂停，光芒队 比尔，现在该怎么办？
Time out, Blazers. what are we gonna do now, Bill?
比赛还有十秒 我想他们真的要动起来...
COMMENTATOR 2.; Ten seconds in the game. I think these guys really need to get their act...
专注在比赛上，狗爬式的 要做春梦晚点再说
Get your head in the game, doggy style. You can finish your wet dream later.
- 抱歉 - 这是为了比赛
-l'm sorry. -This is it for this game.
史考特？ 能和你谈一下吗？
Hey, scott? Can l talk to you for a sec?
你疯了吗？ 我在比赛耶
-Are you nuts? l'm in the middle of a game. -Last home game of the season.
本季最后一场地主赛 真的让他们团结起来
(GlGGLEs) Really gotta get their act together.
两队都是89分，还剩3.9秒 看看最后结果会如何
Tie game, 89 all, 3.9 seconds left. Let's see what's gonna happen here.
- 中央队拿到球 - 光芒加油！
-Central's got the ball. -CHEERLEADERs: Go, Blazers!
他们有优势
They have the advantage.
看来...突破夹击！
Looks like... Double screen!
席尔森抢到球，传给史考特史提弗
shearson gets the ball. He passes it to scott stifler. It's good! It's in!
进了！ 球进算！
比赛结束 91比89，东瀑光芒队获胜
The game's over. 91-89 for East Great Falls Blazers.
太惊人了，各位！ 这表示我们晋级季后赛
This is incredible, folks! This means we're going on to the playoffs!
真不敢相信！ 太刺激了
Unbelievable! It's exciting.
今天的惊喜真是层出不穷！
what a chain of events that has occurred here today!
亲爱的，我们必须谈谈
Honey, l need to talk to you.
好，当然
Yeah, sure.
这...这是圣经吗？
ls... ls that a Bible?
什么？ 不，不是...
What? No. No, it's...
儿子，看圣经没关系啊 天啊，你的反应
Well, honey, it's okay to read the Bible. l mean, gosh, you act like
好像我抓到你看A书
l caught you reading pornography.
你要谈什么？
What did you wanna talk about?
我刚收到信用卡帐单...
Well, l Just got my credit card statement and...
你的副卡有一笔是内衣店的消费
And here on your card there's a charge here for a lingerie store.
对，我... 我会还你的，妈
Yeah, l'm... l'm gonna pay you back for that, Mom.
是你在约会的对象？
ls there a girl you're seeing?
不，妈，这很复杂
No. Mom, it's complicated.
- 你买来自用的？ - 不是！
-Did you buy something for yourself? -No!
你想探索是很正常的
Because it's a very normal area of exploration.
书上说多数的恋物狂 本质上并非同志
My book says that most fetishes are not homosexual in nature,
你知道男孩会这样，他们会...
and, well, you know, boys, they tend to...
对，妈，就是这样 你懂了，我爱穿女性内衣
Yes, Mom, that's it. You figured it out. l love wearing women's underwear.
丁字裤、连身衬衣
Thongs, G-strings, a little teddy now and then.
触感好软，像丝一样 越多摺边越好
lt's so soft and silky smooth. The frillier the better.
超性感
sexy.
天啊！ 别这样
Oh, God! Come on.
拍到了
Gotcha.
所以是送女生的
so it was for a girl.
对，妈
Yeah, Mom.
很好
Great.
记得在舞会前 你对我说过的话？
so, you know that thing you told me before the dance?
嗯
Yeah.
对，我在想当时的谈话
Right, well, l was thinking about that conversation.
怎么样？
so, what about it?
我认为也许你该等一等
l was Just thinking, you know, maybe you should wait.
我知道，我也想过
l know. You know, l've thought about it, too,
但我还是觉得，我把整件事情
but l still feel like l'm making this whole thing
看得太严重了 这会影响我的所有思想
into, like, this huge deal. l mean, it's consuming my every thought.
我不知道，罗伯
l don't know, Rob.
我想我最好还是快点克服
l still feel like it's best if l Just get it over with.
对，我能了解
Yeah. l can see that.
你懂了，我爱穿女性内衣
ROB ON PHONE.; You figured it out. I love wearing women's underwear.
丁字裤、连身衬衣
Thongs, G-strings, a little teddy now and then.
触感好软，像丝一样 越多摺边越好
It's so soft and silky smooth. The frillier the better.
这又是怎么回事？ 屁蛋？
What is up with this crap, butt nugget?
那完全是断章取义 好吗？ 我是开玩笑的
That was taken completely out of context. All right? l was being facetious.
这表示他不是认真的
That means he wasn't being serious.
我知道什么是开玩笑，屎蛋
l know what facetious means, dick face.
你打算吓退全校的女孩？
Are you trying to repel all the pussy in school?
- 不... - 滴答，狗仔男
-No... -Tick tock, doggy boy.
你一直在浪费时间
You cock is on the clock.
借过，学着点
Excuse me. Take notes.
- 嘿，伊茉珍 - 史提弗
-Hey, lmogen. -stifler.
今天的每日一字是“腿”
The word for the day is ''legs.''
所以呢？
so?
所以何不回我住处 我们好好研究这个字？
so, why don't we go back to my place and spread the word?
你省口气吧
Well, how about you save your breath?
等一下你需要力气 吹涨你的充气娃娃
You're gonna need it to inflate your date later.
各位，该我们成功达阵了
Gentlemen, it is time we got laid.
真的？ 我们不是一直都在尝试？
Really? And what is it we've been trying to do all this time?
不，我们必须达阵 就在这里，1995年9月9日
No, no. We need to get laid. Right here. september 9th, 1995.
讲讲要怎么执行？
Can you give us the executive summary?
不是那个，这个
No, not that. This.
我们要来一趟公路旅行
LUBE: We are going on a road trip.
欢迎光临加拿大
你打算在加拿大待多久？
How long do you intend on staying in Canada?
几个小时
Just a couple of hours.
入境的目的为何？
What's the nature of your visit?
我们开了好几英哩 来寻找可爱的辣妹哩
We've driven many miles in search of vertical smiles.
我们这里是公里制
We use kilometers here.
我们开到头昏 来替小弟弟开个荤？
Then we've driven many clicks to wet our dicks?
- 耶！ - 好耶！
LUBE: Yes! ROB: Yeah!
- 有用吧？ - 再见
-That works, right? -Bye-bye.
该死的美国佬
Fucking Americans.
美元的汇率对我们很有利
You know, the exchange rate on the dollar is really gonna help us out.
对
Yeah.
好，前面右转
Okay, up ahead, turn right.
- 你确定？ - 对，右转
-You sure? -Yes. Turn right.
好，兄弟们，我们上吧
Okay, boys. Let's do this.
你确定这样好吗？
Are you sure this is a good idea?
拜托，少孬了，我们要开荤喽
Come on, you pussy. Let's get laid.
宝典说要找莫妮
The bible says to ask for Monique.
嗨，你是莫妮吗？
Hi. Are you Monique?
不，我不是 但是莫妮在里面
(lN FRENCH ACCENT) No, moi, no, no, no. Mais, Monique, she is inside.
进来，孩子们
Come. Come, boys.
男孩们，欢迎光临
Boys, entrez chez nous.
这很美吧？ 我去找莫妮
C'est magnifique, no? l will get Monique.
她一定很高兴见到你们
she will be so happy to see you.
你们先随意坐吧
ln the meantime, make yourselves at home.
天啊，大奶妹，我们来对地方了
Jesus, tits. We came to the right place.
那是麋鹿吗？
ls that a moose?
保险套？
Condom?
好，谢谢你
Why, thank you.
先生
Gentlemen.
谢谢
Thank you.
非常感谢
Very much.
谢谢
Thank you.
等不及见莫妮了
LUBE: Can't wait to see Monique.
我们来找莫妮的
(sTAMMERlNG) We're here to see Monique.
我就是莫妮
(lN FRENCH ACCENT) l am Monique.
哦，那...没关系
Well, that's... That's okay.
来嘛，我帮你们弄好喝的
Come, come. l make you a nice drink.
等我们一下好吗？
Could you Just give us Just one minute?
- 可能很有教育性 - 真的？
-This could be very educational for all of us. -Really?
- 就他了 - 不，为何我先？
-He's up. -No, no. Why am l first?
是你的主意
NATHAN: lt was your idea.
不...别侮辱莫妮 宝典有一整章都在讲她
Don't... Don't insult Monique. she has an entire chapter in the bible.
- 来嘛，你会爽翻天的 - 你们两个疯子慢慢玩
Come on, you're going to have a nice time. LUBE: (LAUGHs) You two crazy kids have fun.
欢迎呀
And welcome.
所以规矩是怎样？ 我要付钱给你？
so... so, how does this work? Am l supposed to pay you?
不，还不用
No, no, no. Not yet.
我懂了
l see.
你的想像力很丰富，孩子
You've got one active imagination, boy.
我晃神多久了？
How long was l out?
大概八秒钟而已
Only about eight seconds that time.
我的阴阜 阴道润滑剂
不、不行、不行
No, no, no, no, no, no, no. No. No. No, no, no.
耶、耶
Yes. Yes.
莫妮！ 真是太棒了
ROB: Monique! That's really nice.
就是这样
ROB: That's it.
抱歉，我平常可以更久一点
l'm so sorry. l usually last a lot longer.
嘿
Hey.
嘿，我该拍拍你肩膀之类的？
Hey, was l supposed to tap you on the shoulder or something?
哦，不好了
Oh, no. No.
救命啊！ 救命啊！
Help! Help! Help, help, help!
- 快！ 快去看看！ - 来了！
NATHAN: Go, go, go! Go! LUBE: l'm coming!
- 天啊 - 我的天！
-Jesus. Dude. -Oh, God!
你需要观众啊？
What, do you need an audience?
不，等一下，我想她死了！
No, no. Wait, guys. l think she's dead!
你说什么？
Excuse me?
我的天，这可不妙
Oh, my God. This is not good.
我无法拉开她 她应该是心脏病发
l can't get her off. l think she had a heart attack.
救命啊！ 她咬紧我了，快弄开她！
Help! she's got lockJaw. Get her off of me!
- 我的天 - 她牙关紧闭
-Oh, my God. Oh, my God. -lt's lockJaw.
牙关紧闭！ 牙关紧闭
LockJaw! LockJaw, lockJaw, lockJaw, lockJaw, lockJaw!
- 好 - 弄开她！
-Okay. -Get her off!
对不起！
l'm sorry!
电话，等等，退后！
Phone. Phone. Wait. Clear!
可恶，我在干嘛？
shit. What am l doing?
后退、后退！
Clear, clear!
好，蹲下来 抓住她的腿，一、二、三
Okay. Come down here. Grab her legs. One, two, three.
全搞砸了，天啊
Forget it. lt's totally screwed up. Oh, God.
你对妈妈怎么了？
What you do to maman?
妈妈！ 你杀了妈妈！ 你杀了妈妈！
(CRYING) Maman! You killed maman! You killed maman!
死美国佬！ 给我回来 我要杀了你们！ 懦夫！
Fucking Americans! Come back here. l'll kill you! l'll kill you, you cowards!
我杀了她
ROB: l killed her.
我用精子杀了她！
l killed her with my sperm!
嘿，生死有命 她也活得够精彩了
Hey, man, when it's your time to go, it's your time to go. she led a full life.
你怎么知道？
How do you know that?
不然你要我说什么？ 人是你杀的耶！
Man, what do you want me to say? You're the one that murdered her!
我不敢相信宝典记载 我们应该和她做爱
l can't believe that was the woman the bible said we should have sex with.
就在这里 “1995年9月9日”
Right here. ''september 9th, 1995.''
让我看看
Let me see that.
不，那是7！ 是1975年，70年代的事了
No. No, that's a seven! That's 1975. lt's from the '70s.
- 我以为那是9 - 闭嘴！ 闭嘴！
-l thought it was a nine. -NATHAN: shut up! shut up!
- 我什么也没做！ - 闭嘴！ 我要回家
-l didn't do anything! -shut up! Just shut up! l wanna go home.
我不要待在这里
l don't wanna be here.
天啊！ 我撞到一只松鼠
(THUDs) Oh, my God! l Just hit a squirrel.
还真不顺利
LUBE: Well, that went well.
各位，我想该试试我的解读了
ROB: Guys, l think it's time we try my interpretation.
听着，纳森 你一直想求黛娜和你上床
Look, Nathan, you've been trying to convince Dana to sleep with you,
但你没有认真听她讲话 你懂吗？
instead of Just listening to her. Right, you know?
你试过从她的观点看吗？ 表现出...
Trying to see things from her point of view? showing Just...
一点尊重
Just a little respect.
还有你，你还想用花招 骗女人和你上床
And you, you're still trying to trick women into sleeping with you,
你从来不坦白
instead of Just being honest.
你还是太孬种 不敢告诉海蒂你喜欢她
And you're still too much of a pussy to tell Heidi you're into her.
图书馆入口
你晚上要去史提弗他家？
You going to stifler's house tonight?
对，也许和黛娜一起去
Yeah. l'll probably go with Dana.
所以你摆脱掉处女的事了没？
so any luck losing that thing you were trying to get rid of?
- 罗伯 - 只是问问嘛
-Rob. -l'm Just asking.
也许你管好自己就行了
Maybe you should mind your own business.
你今天怎么搞的？
What's with you today?
我想告诉你 一些我很早就想讲的事
l wanna tell you something that l've been wanting to say for a long time.
好
Okay.
我真的很喜欢你
l really like you.
我也喜欢你
l really like you, too.
不，不是那样，我真的喜欢你
No, not like that. l really like you.
- 罗伯... - 我认为你很棒
-Rob... -l think you're great.
你个性很好 你的笑话常逗我笑，你很漂亮
You have a great personality. l laugh at all your Jokes. You're pretty.
天啊，你好漂亮，闻起来好香
Oh, God, you're pretty. You even smell great.
我不知道，我只是... 有你在身边我就很开心
l don't know. l'm Just... l'm happy when l'm around you.
不知你有没有相同感觉 但如果你有...
Now, l don't know if you feel the same way, but if you do...
让我们别浪费时间了，好吗？
Let's not waste any more time. Right? Let's Just
我们就来交往看看
see where our feelings take us.
我也有相同感觉
l feel the same way.
- 真的？ - 对
-You do? -Yes.
这太棒了，你为何都不说？
This is great. Why didn't you say something?
你怎么不说？
Why didn't you?
是时候了，我该走了 今晚能见到你？
lt's about that time, so l gotta go. But l'll see you tonight?
好
Yes.
爸？
-DANA: Dad? -Mmm-hmm?
她在那里
There she is.
他们看到我了！ 快伏低！
(GAsPlNG) They saw me! Get down! Get down!
- 我的天啊 - 快开车
-Oh, my God. Oh, my gosh. -Drive. Drive.
没事，没事
lt's cool. lt's cool.
纳森，我一直在想
Nathan, look, l've been thinking.
也许我对你太严厉了
Maybe l've been too hard on you.
你吗？
You have?
你显然爱我女儿 你们两个应该在一起
You obviously love my daughter, and you two should be together.
- 我们应该？ - 当然
-We should? -Absolutely.
亲爱的，你不该让男人硬忍着
Honey, it is not right to give a man blue balls.
想要男孩喜欢你，就要开放点 先从纳森的朋友开始
lf you want boys to like you, you gotta put out. Here, start with Nathan's friend.
这太逊了
This is so not cool.
对你麻吉的女朋友 心存幻想？
l mean, fantasizing about your best friend's girlfriend?
我的天！
(sCREAMlNG) Oh, my God!
- 爸！ 住手！ - 该死！
-Dad! stop! stop. -Fucknut!
好耶，女孩们
All right, girls.
- 派对看来不错 - 对
-Party looks good. -Yeah.
好了，注意听我说
All right, listen to me. stay focused.
要诚实，要懂得尊重 心里有话就说出来
Be honest, show respect and Just say whatever's on your mind.
少来，混蛋
stop, Jerk.
我甚至无法靠近黛娜
l can't even get near Dana.
她会来的，和海蒂一起来
she'll be here. she's coming with Heidi.
试着从她的观点来看
Just try and think of things from her point of view.
对，我努力看圣经 顺便破解达文西密码
Yeah, and l might as well Just crack the Da Vinci Code while l'm at it.
给她乳香和没药就行了
Just get her some frankincense and myrrh.
真是好主意
That's a great idea.
我出去顺便帮你买些强暴丸
l'll Just pick up some roofies for you while l'm out.
就我所知，你必须有处方笺
You need a prescription for that, from what l hear.
路伯，注意点，你也一样啦
Lube, pay attention. This applies to you, too.
好，我们进去吧 试着忠于自我
All right. Let's try to go in there and Just be real.
好的，欧普拉
All right, Oprah.
嘿，那不是中央高中的辣妹？
Hey. lsn't that that chick from Central?
对
Yeah.
嘿，史提弗
Hey, stifler.
嘿，你好...
Oh, hey, there...
凯蒂
Katie.
凯蒂，对，我知道 只是逗你玩玩
Katie, right. l knew that. Just having some fun with you.
我可以私下和你谈谈吗？
Can l talk to you for a second, like, in private?
当然，这样吧？
Yeah, sure, you know what?
我再去拿罐啤酒 马上就回来找你
Let me Just grab another beer and l'll be right back with you.
别抛下我哦
Don't you flake on me.
老兄，你有在运动吗？ 我看没有哦
Dude, you been working out? Didn't think so.
你们两个，还是超酷，天啊
You two, stay amazing. My God.
你好吗？ 美女
Hey, what's up, beautiful?
我上星期醉到不行
You know, l got so drunk last weekend
竟然把小鸡鸡钉在桌上 然后拿它起火
that l nailed my cock to a table, then set it on fire.
想看一下吗？
Wanna check it out?
看桌子还是鸡鸡？
The table or your cock?
天啊，我爱你的口音
God, l love that accent.
拜托你说一下
Could you do me a favor and Just say,
“打我屁股，史提弗 轻轻打我的小屁股”
''spank me, stifler. spank me wee little bum.''
你怎么知道我爱这一套？
How did you know l like to be spanked?
太棒了！
(lN HlGH-PlTCHED VOlCE) Awesome!
你一直挂在嘴边的男朋友 那个理查人呢？
so where's this boyfriend Richard you keep talking about non-stop all the time?
他不参加高中派对
He doesn't attend high-school parties.
看来你对美国的牛肉棒 很有兴趣
sounds like you might be in the market for some home-grown American beef.
抱歉，我吃素
sorry, l'm vegan.
干杯
Cheers.
如果我改成小黄瓜呢？
What if l use a cucumber?
好，各位，就是今晚了 祝我好运
All right, boys. Tonight's the night. Wish me luck.
祝你好运，兄弟
Good luck, buddy.
祝你好运，老兄 今晚你要转大人了
Good luck, dude. Tonight, you become a man.
没错，今晚我要开荤了！
That's it. Tonight, l'm getting laid!
- 耶，兄弟！ - 好耶，兄弟
-Yeah, buddy! Yes! -Yeah, buddy.
- 对！ - 就在今夜
-Yes! -Right here.
一开始先慢慢来
Just give it to her nice and slow at first.
然后做快一点
Then speed her up.
黛娜！
Dana!
耶！
Yeah!
- 什么？ - 错了
-What? -sorry.
- 我找不到海蒂 - 也许她没来
-l can't find Heidi anywhere. -Maybe she didn't come.
不，她的车在外面
No, no. Her car is outside.
你的进展如何？
How you making out?
你看看
Check it out.
你不觉得 爱西莉和你搭不在一起？
Don't you think maybe Ashley's Just a little bit out of your league?
我不知道，我只是说说 你试过好几年了
l don't know. l'm Just saying, you know, you've been at it for years.
也许她不是你的真命天女
Maybe it's Just not in the cards for you.
我是很讲究的人
l'm a man of refinement.
能找到十分的女孩 为何要屈就六分的？
Why settle for a six when you can get a perfect 10?
好，随便你，祝你好运
Okay, whatever you say, man. Good luck.
好，我要行动了
Right. l'm gonna do it.
嘿，你好吗？ 爱西莉
Hey, what's up, Ashley?
嘿，路伯
Hey, Lube.
你要啤酒吗？
You want a beer?
已经有了
Got a beer.
对
Right.
所以...
so...
你显然知道 我对你非常着迷吧？
You obviously know that l'm, like, totally into you. Right?
对，我早就知道了
Yeah. l've seen the shrine.
好吧
All right.
所以我就老实说了 我决定有话直说
Okay, so l'm Just gonna be honest with you. l'm Just gonna lay it out on the line.
不耍花招，没有隐瞒
No tricks, no hidden agenda at all.
我刚好是敏感老练的爱人
l happen to be a sensitive and expert lover.
我保证满足你各方面的需求
l can guarantee that l will satisfy you in every way possible,
除非你满意我的努力
and l shall not stop until l'm certain
否则我绝对不会停止
that you are completely happy with my endeavors.
好吧
Okay.
听着，很有趣的告白
Look, that was a really interesting speech,
我真的不想当众给你难堪，但...
and l don't really wanna embarrass you in front of everyone, but...
我们是不可能的
But it's not gonna happen.
我知道你超酷的
l mean, l think that you're, like, really super cool,
你在班上真的很风趣
and you're really funny in class and everything,
但我不想和你上床
but l don't wanna have sex with you.
好吗？
Okay?
嗯，当然喽
Yeah, yeah. sure. Okay.
- 所以我们没事吧？ - 对，没事
-so are we cool? -Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
好的
All right.
我要再来罐啤酒，你要吗？
Well, l'm gonna go get another beer. Do you want one?
不，我...我有啤酒了
No, no. l'm... l'm good. l'm good.
- 嘿 - 嘿
-Hey. -Hey.
你刚刚说什么？
(CLEARs THROAT) What you said Just now?
啥？
Yeah?
那是真的吗？
Was that true?
保证女孩满意了 不然你保证不会停？
Guaranteed satisfaction and you won't stop until a girl is completely satisfied?
对
Yeah.
好啊，管它的
All right. Well, what the hell.
到楼上和我会合 左边第一间卧室
Meet me upstairs in the first bedroom to the left.
我和艾咪在一起 我要上床了！
老实说，对 我想对你施压
NATHAN: The truth is, yes, l was trying to pressure you,
因为我真的很想做爱
because l really, really wanna have sex.
但我真正想要的 是和你做爱
But l really wanna have sex with you.
同时，我们在一起 总是谈到我的需要
And, also, l mean, with us, hooking up has always been about me.
这次我想忘了自己 试着改变，先让你觉得舒服
l wanna forget myself for once and try to make you feel good for a change.
也许试着让你感受到 你所给我的感觉
Like, maybe try and make you feel the way that you make me feel.
你不该...你不该... 那是我的手机
You shouldn't... You shouldn't... lt's my phone.
别看我的手机
Don't read my phone.
这是什么意思？ “和她疯狂大干吧” ？
What's this supposed to mean? ''Give her a dose of manthrax''?
我不知...那...
Well, l don't... What does that...
我不知道那是... 你懂它的意思？
l don't know what that... Do you know what that means?
“我要上床了” ？
''l'm getting laid''?
事情还没发生 你就大肆宣传起来？
You're advertising this before it even happens?
- 不是 - 哇
-No. -Wow.
你八成是另类的混蛋
You must be some special kind of asshole.
不！ 我没有...那是...
No. No, no, no! No. l didn't... lt was...
再见，逊咖
Later, loser.
快点，好，现在慢一点，对
Faster. Okay. Now, slower. Yes, yes.
慢一点，轻碰小穴穴，对
slower. Tickle the bunny. Yes, yes.
天啊，快腾云驾雾了
Oh, God, the man in the boat is out.
划、划，往前划，天旋地转了
Paddle, paddle, do the alphabet. swirl.
回到穴穴，对了 好，现在左边一点
Back to the bunny. That's it. Okay. Now, more to the left.
再左边一点！
More to the left!
- 我的左边还是你的？ - 我的！
-My left or your left? -My left, my left, my left!
好的
All right.
嘿，有没有看到海蒂？
Hey, have you seen Heidi?
谢了
Thanks.
嘿，罗伯
Hey, Rob.
海蒂？
Heidi?
嘿，狗爬式的 我说过，你不行动就没机会了
Hey, doggy style. l told you, you snooze, you lose.
除非你要执勤扫荡 关上门啦，变态
so unless you want mop-up duty, close the door, pervert.
嘿，你要去哪里？
sTlFLER: Hey, where are you going?
这是个超烂的主意
This was a horrible idea.
罗伯？ 借过一下
Rob? Excuse me.
借过，罗伯、罗伯
Excuse me. Rob. Rob.
- 滚开 - 我没有...
-Go away. -l didn't. l...
我现在不想看到你
l don't wanna see your face right now.
罗伯
Rob.
你在做什么？
What are you doing?
你不是要忘了自己 先让我舒服吗？
What happened to forgetting about yourself and making me feel good?
但我以为刚刚...
But l thought l Just...
什么？ 你以为什么？ 纳森
What? You thought that what, Nathan?
你可以假装在乎我的感觉 以及我的守贞
That you could Just pretend that you cared about my feelings and my pledge
等我疏于防备 你好再试一次看看？
and then Just go and try again when my guard was down?
不，你不了解，我...
No. You don't get it. l...
不，你才不了解，你得不到的
No. No, you're the one that's not gonna get it.
老兄，你要放慢脚步
Dude, you need to slow down.
对，说真的，我们回家吧
Yeah, seriously. Let's Just go home.
你这位先生... 宝典的事你说对了
You, sir... You, sir, were right about the bible.
因为混蛋才能上床搞！
Because assholes get laid!
对
Yes.
不，老兄，你是对的
No. No, no, dude. You were right.
- 里面有些道理的 - 你在说什么？
-There's something to it. -What are you talking about?
我们试过当好人了 我相信我们都还是处男
We tried the nice guy thing and l believe we're all still virgins.
当好人差点让我上床成功呢
Well, the nice guy vibe got me past the bouncer, man.
嘿
Hey.
各位先生，你们输了 证明就在果冻中
Well, gentlemen, you failed, and the proof, as they say, is in the Jell-o.
我们晚点见，好人
so l will see you later, nice guys.
- 嘿 - 嘿
-Hey. -Hey.
我知道你要我
l know you want me.
我愿意和你上楼 让你大干一场
l'm gonna let you take me upstairs and do me right now.
- 真的？ - 对
-Really? -Yeah.
吻我
Kiss me.
想来点痛苦的吗？
sTlFLER: Y'all ready for some pain?
小姐们
Hey, ladies.
我的天
GlRL: Oh, my God.
天啊！
sTlFLER: Oh, my God!
看看她们的咪咪！
Look at those taters!
从后面上我
Do me from behind.
什么？
What?
我以为你喜欢狗爬式
l thought you liked it doggy style.
你以为你在干什么？
你杵在后面干嘛？ 快点啊
What are you doing back there? Let's go.
你不会把小鸡鸡放进去吧？
You're not putting your dick in that, are you?
你开啥玩笑？ 太恶心了
Are you kidding me? Gross.
给你，这会舒服点
Here. This'll help.
谢了
Thanks.
儿子，我知道我无法阻止你 去做某些事情
Honey, l know that l can't stop you from doing certain things,
但我坚持你要注意安全
but l can insist that you are safe.
你喝酒又开车吗？
Did you drink and drive?
没有，约翰卡特罗载我回家
No. John Costello drove me home.
我要告诉你 如果你要和人发生关系
Well, l want you to know that if you find yourself in any carnal situation,
你...要做好保护措施
that you... You will use protection.
你在说什么？
What do you mean by carnal?
这个
This.
你开啥玩笑？ 太恶心了
(GROANs) GIRL.; Are you kidding me? Gross.
现在都没隐私了吗？
ls there no such thing as privacy anymore?
我会告诉你爸爸 你今天不能起床见他
l will tell your father that you're Just not up to seeing him today.
你身体不舒服
You're not feeling well.
谢谢
Thanks.
她怎样啊？
How was she?
- 谁怎样？ - 呕吐女孩
-How was who? -Vomit girl.
你怎么知道的？
How do you know about that?
不然你以为是谁 把短片寄给老妈？
Who do you think is forwarding all those videos to Mom?
我准备放弃了
ROB: l'm ready to give up.
我以为我有答案的
l thought l had the answers.
可惜宝典有九成九都看不清楚了
lt's too bad that 99% of the bible's completely unreadable.
就是这样
That's it.
我们必须重建宝典
We need to reconstruct the bible.
为什么？
Why?
秘密都在里面
The secrets are in there.
想上床没有单一解答
l mean, there's no one single answer to getting laid.
对吧？ 我们必须了解 整本书的内容
Right? We need the whole book to understand.
或许里面还有很多 我们必须知道的东西
Probably has a lot of crap in there that we need to know, too,
像姿势、技巧、插入角度
like positions, techniques, angle of insertion.
没错，宝典的作用就在这里 帮助像我们这样的人
Exactly. That's what the bible was created for, to help guys like us.
我们欠大家一个交待 我毁了宝典
And we owe it to the others. l ruined the bible.
这是我欠未来新生代的 我要重拾智慧
l owe it to future generations to restore its wisdom.
老兄，我愿意帮忙，但要怎么做？
Dude, l'm all for it, but how?
从哪里开始？
Where do we start?
从最初开始
From the beginning.
这一定是宝典的原创者
LUBE: This must be the guy who created the bible.
诺亚雷文斯坦 1969年11月6日
哈罗？
Hello?
嗨，我找诺亚雷文斯坦？
ROB.; Hi. May I speak to Noah Levenstein, please?
我就是
speaking.
你是首创宝典的人吗？
Are you the one who created the bible?
雷文斯坦 地毯大卖场
不，那应该是上帝
No, that would be God.
不，等等
No, no, no. Hold on.
我是指那本宝典
l'm referring to the bible.
我从东瀑高中打来的
I'm calling from East Great Falls High school.
把上你
那是我国中的暑假，1969年
NOAH: lt was the summer of my Junior year, 1969,
我的死党和我 去阿姆斯特丹旅行
and my buddies and l, we take this trip to Amsterdam,
我们遇到一批 还算迷人的荷兰花痴
where we run into a group of semi-attractive Dutch nymphos
她们愿意以身体交换 几张吉米罕醉克斯的黑胶唱片
who were willing to trade their bodies for a handful of Jimi Hendrix LPs.
不用说，我们和这些女孩 狂欢了一个周末
Well, needless to say, we had ourselves one super weekend with those gals,
也就是开荤了，懂我意思吧
sexually speaking, if you get my drift.
坏消息是我们不知道自己在干嘛
But the sad news was, we had no idea what we were doing.
我们不懂技巧
We had no technique.
有一天我们出外观光
And then one day, we were out sight-seeing,
遇到红灯区的几名妓女
and we run into this Dutch hooker in the red-light district,
她提到这本书
and she tells us about this book.
一本性爱指南 十九世纪某个神父写的
lt was a sex manual, evidently written in the 19th century by some priest.
我们从头读到尾
Well, we read that thing cover to cover,
然后回到东瀑高中
and then when we got back to East Great Falls,
我决定自己写本书
l had the bright idea to write my own book
加上我自己的观察、经验和忠告
and add my own observations and experiences and advice
把书放在图书馆 造福之后的处男学弟
and leave it in the library for some other hapless virgin in the class below us.
但我没想到 这本书能流传四十年
But l had no idea it had been passed down for 40 years.
你的书是传奇，雷文斯坦先生
Your book is a legend, Mr. Levenstein.
你带来了？
Do you have it here?
对
Yeah.
我可以看看吗？
May l see it?
我的天
Oh, my.
孩子们
Boys.
这是真正的历史啊
This is a real piece of history here.
这本书怎么变这样？
What happened to it?
这就是我们来的原因
Well, that's why we're here.
宝典算是毁了
The bible kinda got ruined,
所以我们打给名单上的人 希望重建这本书
so we wanna call everyone on the list and try to reconstruct it.
我想你们可能需要帮助
Well, l think you boys might need some help.
女孩有个优势 她们彼此会聊天
Well, girls have the advantage, because girls talk to each other,
别自欺欺人了 她们会聊那话儿的
and don't kid yourself, they talk about the penis.
它的大小、形状 弯曲的角度
Penis size, penis shape, the angle of the bend.
是否对你眨眼，她们都会聊
Whether it winks at you. They talk.
听好，想和女人做爱 你必须真的关心她
Now, to really make love to a woman, you gotta really care about her.
但...性爱很好 但和你爱的人做？ 那才棒呆了
But... Hey, sex is great, but sex with someone you love? That's awesome.
老兄，真是发人深省
Dude, that is so profound.
我说了算
Telling you.
对，上路绝对很孤独
Yeah, definitely gets lonely on the road.
当然，我和各种菜色做过
sure, l made love to all kinds of different food groups.
你和奶油三明治做过吗？
Did you ever try making love to a peanut-butter sandwich?
无与伦比
Nothing comes close.
什么？
What?
也许去骨的腿肉有得比 但那需要很多准备
Well, maybe a deboned ham hock, but that takes a whole lot of prep.
膝盖弯曲
Bend your knees.
下次手淫时，采印地安坐姿
Next time you spank it, sit lndian-style.
你不会射，永远不会射
You won't come, not in a million years.
性器官就像乐器
MAN: Our sex organs are like musical instruments.
随便找个技师 当然都能吹你的乐器
sure, you can have any technician blow on your horn,
但如果把乐器交到 真正的专家手中呢？
but to place your instrument into the hands of a true expert?
我的年轻朋友，那才叫和谐
That, my young friend, is true harmony.
男孩子彼此不聊这些
NOAH: Guys don't talk to each other
因为他们视彼此为竞争对手
because they view each other as competitors,
我认为这很疯狂，你懂吗？
which l think is crazy. You know?
因为男人要互相帮助 共同合作才能达阵
Because men need to help each other and work together to get laid.
诺亚雷文斯坦，70年那一届
NO AH.; Noah Levenstein, class of '70.
- 彼特山培利？ - 对，诺亚雷文斯坦
ROB.; Pete sambrelli? NO AH.; That's right, the Noah Levenstein.
你有他的电话？
ROB.; Do you have a number for him?
嗨，我想询问 他对润滑剂的意见
Hi. This is regarding his advice on the lubricants.
找到喇舌龙卷风了，在里贾纳
We found the tongue tornado in Regina.
绝不能见色忘友
You said bros befo' hos.
你不是这样说的？ 不能见色忘友 结果你睡了我女朋友
lsn't that what you said? Bros befo' hos. And then you screwed my girlfriend.
整个合唱团都睡过她，卡利多 你的重点呢？
Well, so did the entire glee club, Carlito. What's your point?
最重要是来电 自信是关键
lt's all about chemistry, and confidence is the key.
学会尊重 你听过那首歌吧？
MAN.; R-E-s-P-E-C-T, you've heard that song, right?
小子，我们得到另一项确认
Boys, we got another confirmation.
你必须好好对待女人
MAN: You gotta treat your lady right.
你必须温柔、和善 尊重你所爱的人
You've got to be gentle, kind and respectful to the one you love.
- 你在和谁讲话？ - 闭嘴啦
-Who are you talking to? -shut the fuck up.
这样能让她很兴奋
This is how you get her really excited.
把手指叉进她的菊花，相信我
stick your finger in her ass. Trust me.
一根还是两根？
Was that two fingers or one?
抱歉，这是机密
LUBE: l'm sorry. Confidential matter.
电话、电话，好
NOAH: Phone, phone. Okay.
然后怎么了？
LUBE: Then what happened?
喂，对，77年那一届
Hello. Yeah. Class of '77.
对，等等，我拿枝笔
Yeah, hold on. Let me get a pen.
请接彼得欧唐诺
Pete O'Donnell, please.
你哪位？
Who is this?
欧唐诺先生，我是马修路伯斯基
Mr. O'Donnell, this is Marshall Lubetski.
我只想找你聊聊 你写在宝典的内容
l Just wanted to talk to you about what you wrote in the bible.
你知道，就是和强森小姐肛交
You know, about having anal sex with Miss Johnson.
...多谢！ 标上s！
...very much! Mark s.!
2010年 新宝典
这不是性爱宝典
This is not a sex manual.
而是人生宝典
lt is a life manual.
我结婚35年了
Now, l've been married for 35 years
不只因为我是帅哥一个
and not Just because l'm this handsome dude
知道如何满足女人
who knows how to satisfy a woman.
我结婚35年 是因为我爱我太太
l've been married 35 years because l love my wife
我尊重太太
and l respect my wife.
不管在阿姆斯特丹 或东瀑高中
And whether it's Amsterdam or East Great Falls,
结论都一样
it all comes down to this.
如果你够诚实，并尊重女孩
lf you're honest and treat a girl with respect,
那么该发生的就会发生 因为那再自然不过了
then whatever happens is meant to happen, because it's all perfectly natural.
孩子们，我为你们准备这场征途
Boys, l've prepared you for this quest.
在你们眼前 是人生最大的考验
And before you lies the biggest test of your lives.
这本书是强而有力的武器
This book is a powerful weapon,
所以要用在好的方面
so use it for good,
别做坏事
not evil.
宝典
好耶
Yes.
你还在找吸尘器？
ROB: You still looking for the vacuum?
不，我在柯弟房间找到了，真怪
No. l found it in Cody's room. so strange.
我不记得曾放在那里
l mean, l Just don't remember leaving it there.
我显然很健忘
(LAUGHs) Losing my mind, clearly.
妈，我可以参加滑雪之旅吗？
Hey, Mom, can l go on the ski trip?
可以
Yes.
但不能喝酒 如果真喝了酒，就不能开车
But no drinking, and if you do drink, no driving.
别担心，如果我做错事 一定会被人放上网路...
Don't worry. lf l do anything wrong, l'm sure it'll end up on YouTube, so...
我到了打给你
Call you when l get there.
干杯吧！
Drinking round!
- 算我一份 - 你在这里做什么？
-Deal me in. -What are you doing here?
我是凯蒂
Katie.
我知道，但你来干嘛？
l know. But what are you doing here?
- 我想玩牌 - 是哦
-l wanna play. -Right.
就发牌给她嘛，史提弗，怎么了？
Just deal her in, stifler. What's the big deal?
对，发给她
AMY: Yeah, deal her in.
嗨，纳森
Hi, Nathan.
谢谢你送的花
Thanks for the flowers.
抱歉我一直像个混蛋 我已经学到教训了
l'm sorry about being a Jerk. And, for the record, l've learned my lesson.
我准备去尊重你 支持你的守贞誓言
l'm ready to respect you and support you on your pledge.
真的？ 为什么？
Really? But why?
我爱的是你 不是为了性爱
l'm in this for you. l'm not in it Just to have sex.
我了解我爱的是你
Well, l realized that l'm in this for you,
如果守贞成为阻碍 那我们感情能好到哪里？
and if the pledge gets in the way of that, then how good can it really be?
看来我们有基本共识了 先缓缓，看看未来会如何
sounds like a good basis for the two of us to Just relax and see what happens.
看，我买了本书
Look. l bought a book.
我想我们可以...
l was thinking that we could
《印度爱经》 完全图解
...从第一页开始 看看周末能试到哪里
start on page one and then see how far we get this weekend.
前三章是前戏
The first three chapters are foreplay.
哇
Wow.
事实上我也在读一本书
You know, l've actually been reading a book, as well.
你听过喇舌龙卷风吗？
Have you ever heard of the tongue tornado?
好，我们走吧
Okay, let's go.
这应该很好玩的
This is supposed to be fun.
一点也不好玩
This isn't fun.
你耐心等，你现在拥有智慧了
Just you wait. You possess wisdom now.
相信宝典说的
Trust in the book.
那是什么意思？ 我太黏人吗？
l mean, what does that mean, anyway? Do you think l'm too clingy?
不，当然不是
No. No, of course not.
你知道怎么玩牌吗？
Do you even know how to play poker?
我知道怎么玩
KATlE: l know the game.
如果我输了，我会脱光光
And l tell you what, if l lose, l'll take off all my clothes.
- 好样的 - 真好
AMY: snap. AsHLEY: Nice.
如果我输了呢？
And if l lose?
你要向我道歉
You apologize to me.
- 为了什么？ 不鸟你？ - 对
-For what? Blowing you off? -KATlE: Yes.
如果这还不够，那是我的第一次
lf it's not enough, it was my first time.
我值得更好的
l deserve better.
但如果我赢了，你不但要道歉
But if l win, not only do you apologize to me,
你还要在雪地裸奔
you gotta run through the snow naked.
- 耶 - 说定了
-Yeah. -lt's a deal.
开始脱吧，宝贝
start stripping, sweetheart.
还没完呢
lt's not over yet.
感觉好运来了？
Feeling lucky?
你最好祈祷最后一张是5，宝贝
You better hope for a five on the river, baby.
她拿到5了！ 真不敢相信
AsHLEY: she got the five! Unbelievable.
我的天
Oh, my God.
- 脱吧 - 等等
-strip. -Hold on a second.
- 脱 - 脱
-strip. -strip.
- 脱！ 脱！ 脱！ - 脱！ 脱！ 脱！
ALL: (CHANTlNG) strip! strip! strip! strip!
strip! strip! strip! strip!
你要我脱？ 你要来点这个？
You want me to strip? You want some of this?
该出发溜鸟了，宝贝！
lt's time to get it going, baby!
好，我们走吧！ 宝贝
All right, let's go! Here we go, baby.
等等，让我们讲清楚
sTlFLER: Wait, let's talk this over.
可恶，外面冷死了
shit. lt's freezing out here.
现在道歉吧
Now apologize.
- 对不起 - 为了什么？
-l'm sorry. -For what?
抱歉事后没打电话给你
l'm sorry for not calling you afterwards.
还有呢？
And what else?
抱歉我像个混蛋，行吗？
l'm sorry for being a dick, okay?
现在快点开门啦
Now, open the stinking door.
开门啊！
Open the door!
现在告诉大家 你高潮之后，如何哭得像小女孩
Now, tell everyone how you cry like a little girl after you come.
我爽了之后哭得像小女孩，行吗？
l cry like a girl after l come, okay?
那是非常激动的经验
lt's a very intense experience for me.
快打911
Call 91 1 .
嘿，我们晚点在小屋见
Hey, l'll meet you at the lodge later.
好啊，你走吧
Yeah, yeah, sure. Go.
海蒂，等等
ROB: Heidi. Wait up.
你介意我一起搭吗？
Do you mind if l ride up with you?
好啊
Okay.
嘿，你好吗？
Hey. What's up?
我们...我们要坐同一个缆车
We... We're in the same gondola.
是啊，你看看
Yeah, look at that.
天啊
Oh, God.
我没和史提弗上床
l didn't sleep with stifler.
嗯，我听说了
Yeah. l heard.
- 你还在恨我？ - 没有
-But you still hate me? -No.
没有，你怎么这样说？
No. Why would you say that?
那晚之后你没和我说过话
You haven't said a word to me since that night.
我知道，抱歉
l know. l'm sorry.
我想我只是... 我需要时间厘清我的感觉
l guess l Just... l needed time to work through my feelings.
然后呢？ 你决定呢？
And? What did you decide?
吉布说史提弗六周内 都要坐在橡皮护垫上
Gibbs says that stifler has to sit on a foam rubber donut for six weeks.
他说他们在考虑 冻伤的部分是否要截肢
And he says they're talking about amputating his feet from frostbite.
吉布是个骗子 史提弗不需截肢
Gibbs is a liar. stifler doesn't need amputation.
太可惜了，我工艺课都拿甲的
That's too bad. l got an A in shop.
天啊，那是鼾声吗？
Oh, my. Was that a snort?
吊车控制室 闲人勿入
来幸灾乐祸的？
Come to gloat?
不，我来找根香烟
No. Just looking for a fag.
虽然我被麋鹿从后面上了 不代表我就是同志
Just 'cause l took a moose pickle up my ass doesn't mean l'm gay.
真好笑，你的屁股还好吧？
Very funny. How's your bum?
感觉像是生了罐美乃滋 谢谢关心
Feels like l gave birth to a mayonnaise Jar, but thanks for asking.
我听说你男友的事了，那真混蛋
Hey, l heard about your boyfriend. That really sucks.
是啊，我还以为 只有高中男生是混蛋
Yeah. l thought only high school boys were Jerks.
结果他们还是长不大
lt turns out they never outgrow it.
伊茉珍，恕我直言 你是我认识最成熟的女孩
lmogen, no offense, and you're the most mature girl l know,
但是24岁的男人 对高中女生是不会认真的
but a 24-year-old dude isn't gonna take a high-school girl seriously.
我想是吧
l suppose not.
你想坐一下吗？
You wanna sit down?
干嘛？
What for?
只是觉得我们现在都需要朋友
l Just thought we could both use a friend right now.
史提弗
stifler.
是我不好，只是反射动作
My bad. Reflex.
我很抱歉
ROB: l'm sorry.
你必须自己做决定
You have to make your own decisions.
我只是... 我以为我们挺来电的
You know, l Just... l thought we had something.
以前是啊
We did.
现在还是
We do.
我在害怕
l was scared.
怕什么？
Of what?
我真的喜欢你
l really like you.
我希望这段很特别
And l want it to be special.
我猜我只想做好准备
l guess l Just wanted to be ready.
所以你差点和史提弗上床 是为了我，想做好准备
so you almost had sex with stifler so you'd be ready for me.
对
Yeah.
那是我听过最蠢的事
That's the dumbest thing l've ever heard.
嗯，听说你就做了些练习
Well, l heard you got some practice.
事实上根本没发生什么事
You know, the truth is, is nothing happened.
我不想随便和人上床
l didn't want it to be random like that.
而且...
And...
我无法想像我的第一次 不是和你一起
l couldn't picture my first time being with anybody else but you.
怎么了？
What was that?
我不知道
l don't know.
- 我们好像困住了 - 对
-Looks like we're stuck. -Yeah.
我们可能要待上一下子
You know, we could be up here for a while.
对
Yeah.
能问你一个问题吗？
LUBE: Hey, can l ask you a question?
当然，问吧
Yeah, sure. Whatever.
你为何和史考特史提弗 那种混蛋约会？
Why do you hook up with assholes like scott stifler anyway?
什么，你又不认识我
Excuse me, but you don't know me.
你和其他人一样
(sCOFFs) You know, you're Just the same as all the rest.
我只是你的战利品
l'm Just some sort of trophy to you.
你不关心我，你只想上我
You don't care about me. You Just wanna sleep with me,
因为你觉得 那是某种地位象征
because you think it's some sort of status symbol.
抱歉
sorry.
天啊
God.
我们还要困多久？
How long are we gonna be up here?
我来求救
l'll get help.
你在做什么？
AsHLEY: What are you doing?
这不会很高 离雪地大约6公尺
lt's not that far down, and there's, like, 20 feet of snow.
你想引我注意啊？
What, is this supposed to impress me?
我是有闪过这个念头
The thought had crossed my mind.
绝对不行，首先，这样不对
Absolutely not. First of all, it's Just wrong.
其次，你根本不该开门的
second of all, you're not even supposed to touch the door.
第三，这样很危险好吗？ 别靠在那里了
And third, it's Just really dangerous, okay? so Just get away from there.
对，我在想什么？
Right. What was l thinking?
你还好吗？
Are you okay?
我想我的腿受伤了
l think l hurt my leg.
白痴
ldiot.
你还好吗？
Are you okay?
你疯了吗？
Are you crazy?
你没事吧？
Are you okay?
对，我很好，没事
Yeah, l'm fine. No, l'm fine. l'm fine.
关于你刚说的 说什么我不关心你
About what you said about how l don't care about you
你只是个战利品，那完全不是真的
and you're Just a trophy, that's actually not true.
我真的喜欢你 我们一起上小学的
l really like you. We went to elementary school together.
我记得六年级的才艺表演 你唱了 《嘿呀！ 》
l remember when you sang Hey Ya! in the sixth-grade talent show.
我记得国一校庆 你从叠罗汉顶端摔下来
l remember when you fell off the pyramid at the homecoming game, freshman year.
你非常不好意思，但我不在乎
You were so embarrassed, but l didn't care.
我喜欢你的反应 好像本来就计划那样
l Just liked how you played it off like it was all part of the routine.
对，你当然是超辣的美女 但我是因为你才喜欢你的
l mean, yeah, sure, you're a super-hot babe, but l actually like you for you.
这也许会吓到你
Look, this may be a shock to you,
但我完全不懂怎么和女孩相处
but l have no idea what l'm doing with girls.
但我真的想学，只要你给我机会
But l really wanna learn. You Just give me a chance.
我只要求这样
That's all l'm asking.
我保证我会当成这辈子的使命
And l guarantee that l will make it my life's mission
在各方面全力满足你
to satisfy you in every way possible.
- 我们回去... - 回小屋吧
-Let's go back to the... -To the cabin.
老兄，你忘了签名
Dude. You forgot to sign it.
你确定我们不能再多保留一年？
You sure we can't Just keep it for one more year?
不，各位，该轮到别人了
No, guys, it's someone else's turn.
这是我的小弟，柯弟
ROB ON COMPUTER.; This is my little brother, Cody,
这是他每天利用吸尘器做的事
and this is what he does with the vacuum every day.
不！ 嘿！ 不要！
No! Hey! No!
救命啊！ 卡住了！ 我拿不下来！
COD Y.; Help! It's stuck! I can't get it off!
救命啊！ 救命！ 它卡住了
Help! Help! It's stuck.
抓到你了
(LAUGHs) Gotcha.
救命！
COD Y.; Help!
点阅人数： 9，937，551
不！
No!
她在利用我，我...那真的很烂
she was using me. l... That was really bad.
天父，汝为何遗弃我？
Father, why hast Thou forsaken me?
到电器行来帮我吹？
Wanna suck me off in the sharper lmage?
罗伯，你又在胡言乱语？
Rob, are you some kind of Jive turkey?
他和本尊只有分寸之差
He's like an inch away from the real McCoy.
你有带保险套吗？
Did you bring condoms?
什么？
What?
我13岁以前都会尿床，行吗？
l wet the bed until l was 13 years old, okay?
就算握有一叠 强纳斯兄弟演唱会的后台通行证
You nancy boys couldn't get lucky at a Jonas Brothers concert
你们两个孬种也把不到女孩
with a fistful of backstage passes.
信上帝得永生
Faith in God and His promise of eternal life.
把保险套套在香蕉上
Now, put the condom on the banana.
谁会想得到？ 时间不早了，该走人了
Who didn't see that coming? Look at the time. Gotta go.
我想你拍够啦啦队的照片了
l think that is quite enough pictures of the cheerleaders.
拍些球赛的照片吧？
How about we get some of the game?
我们在吃东西
We're eating.
你们这些该死的美国...
You've been fucking Americans or...
观察、爱怜...
Watching, loving...
我又演坏了
Bear with me.
如果她难过，买花送她
lf she's down, bring her flowers.
如果她渴了，请她喝香槟
lf she's thirsty, serve her fine champagne.
对，我告诉你 我太太真他妈的辣
Yeah, 'cause, l'm telling you, my wife is pretty effing hot.
我说的是紧实的翘臀 毫无瑕疵
l'm talking a tight, tight ass and squeaky clean.
有加奶油的？ 你最棒了
ls that cream-filled? You rock.
别提那个，好吗？
Oh. Don't mention that, okay?
不管何时想爱抚 请放 《齐柏林飞船第四张专辑》 A面
And whenever it comes to making out, put on side one of Led Zeppelin IV.